A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2009-2013 (bulk 2010-2013)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence-Robert F. McDonnell, 2009-2013 (bulk 2010-2013)
The Library of Virginia
51119
31.7 cu. ft. (33 boxes)
Virginia. Governor (2010-2014: McDonnell)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78, 2.2-3800 and 2.2-3705.1-8
Before serving the materials, Library reference archivists must check the files for privacy protected and confidential information.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Governor January 7 2014.
Biographical/Historical Information
Robert F. McDonnell was elected 71st governor of the Commonwealth of Virginia in November 2009 and inaugurated on 16 January 2010. He served until 11 January 2014.
The office of Constituent Affairs was first established in 1984. The office serves as liaison between the Governor and citizen of the Commonwealth. This office receives and addresses correspondence directed to the Governor. The secretary of the Commonwealth's office performed these services prior to the creation of this office.
Scope and Content
The office of Constituent Affairs, which operates as an extension of the Governor, receives and replies to correspondence sent to the Governor and from citizens of the Commonwealth, political officials, and other organizations. The records are correspondence written to and from the Governor's office covering a broad range of topics such as: discrimination, abortion, crime, economic development, budget cuts, education, capital punishment and other issues that have an impact on the citizens of the Commonwealth. A substantial amount of the collection consists of appeals for assistance in personal legal matters outside the purview of the governor. Of note are also concerns about the U.S. President Barack Obama.
The majority of this series consists of general correspondence from constituents to the Governor and do not include formal responses from the office. In addition to mail from the general public (which includes invitations, requests for assistance on a variety of issues, and stances on policy issues), this correspondence also includes letters from federal and state agencies, local government officials, Virginia General Assembly members, members of the U.S. Congress, and others, including the U.S. President, governors of other states and ambassadors.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series, respecting original order as much as possible:
Series I: General Constituent Correspondence; Series II: Proclamations/Internship Files; Series III: Requests for Photos/Autographs; Series IV: VIP Correspondence; Series V: Uncategorized Correspondence
Series I contains the bulk of the collection, and is arranged numerically. The number systems loosely reflects a chronological order. Series II is also arranged in numerical order. The bulk of series III is arranged in reverse chronological order beginning with 2013. Series IV is arranged in chronological order beginning with 2010. Series V is general correspondence that was not given a number and filed separately, loosely chronologically.
Related Material
The Governor Robert F. McDonnell Administration Web Archive Collection, 2010-2014 contains archived versions of websites for the Governor's Office, his initiative sites, and the sites of his cabinet secretaries. Also included are the related sites for the First Lady (Maureen McDonnell), as well as the Lt. Governor (Bill Bolling), and Attorney General (Ken Cuccinelli).
The Records of Robert F. McDonnell's Deputy Chief of Staff Matt Conrad Collection
The Correspondence and Supporting Documentation of the Executive Office of Governor Robert F. McDonnell Collection
The Records of the Executive Mansion of Governor Robert F. McDonnell
The Records of Governor Robert F. McDonnell's Secretary of Transportation Collection
The Records of Governor Robert F. McDonnell's Secretary of Administration Collection
Contents List
- Series I: General Constituent Correspondence 2010-2013
  - 2000204-2000204 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2000296-2000342 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2000343-2000367 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2000368-2000384 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2000385-2000408 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2000409-2000894 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2016305-2019889 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2019753-2020138 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2020147-2020362 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2020374-2020752 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 2021531-2021639 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 2021640-2021663 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 2021664-2021702 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2021703-2021884 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2022057-2022150 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 2022151-2023321 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2023322-2023380 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2023381-2039669 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 2039670-2042062 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 2042063-2042385 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 2042389-2042699 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 2042760-2042868 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 2042873-2044089 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 2044118-204612 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2046164-2046453 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 2046471-2047582 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 2048036-2048171 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 2048172-2048257 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 2048267-2048374 2010 Feb-Mar (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 248376-2048639 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 2048640-2048660 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 2048663 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 2048668 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 2048669-2048693 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 2048694-2049540 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 2049541-2049894 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 2049906-2050194 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 2050200-2051017 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 2051018-2051049 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 2051056-2051761 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 2051772-2051835 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 2052072-2052742 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 2052743-2052800 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 2052801-2052861 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 2052862-2053385 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 2053398-2053776 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 2054240-2054298 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 2054299-2054705 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 2054710-2054949 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 2054950-2055044 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 2055051-2055094 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 2055095-2055136 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 2055136-2055638 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 2055641-2055685 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 2055690-2055809 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 2055810-2055961 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 2055966-2056020 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 2056021-2056037 2010 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 2056093-2056412 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 2056413-2056443 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 2056445-2056593 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 20256607-2056713 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 2056765-2057128 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 2057131-2057608 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 2057610-2057756 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 2057759-2058005 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 2058007-2058044 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 2058047-2058173 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 2058175-2058325 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 2058327-2058360 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 2058361-2058390 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 2058393-2058547 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 2058549-2059478 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 2059480-2059554 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 2059555-2059591 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 2059523-2059710 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 2059712-2059893 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 2059895-2059929 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 2059930-2060040 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 2060042-20660641 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 2060643-2060774 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 2060775-2060817 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 2060818-2060868 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 20560920-2061008 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 2061009-2061172 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 2061245-2061306 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 2061307-2061478 2010 May-June (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 2061481-2061543 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 2061544-2061672 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 2061674-2061690 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 2061692-2061698 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 2061700-2061887 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 2061910-2062073 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 2062081-2062322 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 2062323-2062339 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 2062363-2062642 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 2062650-2062916 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 2062920-2062999 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 2063007-2063090 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 2063092-2063426 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 2063531-2063853 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 2063854-2063953 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 2064067-2064186 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 2064188-2064269 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 2064274-2064468 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 2064467-20646802 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 2064681-2064894 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 2064896-2064927 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 2064928-2064933 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 2064940-2065170 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 2065172-2065191 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 2065263-2065333 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 2065339-2065425 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 2065428-2065435 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 2065446-2065487 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 2065528-2065586 2010 June-July (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 2065589-2065802 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 2065803-2065865 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 2065867-2065994 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2065995-2066172 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2066174-2066396 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 2066400-2066768 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2066771-2066960 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2066961-2067116 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 2067117-2067162 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2067163-2067564 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2067568-2067753 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2067751-2067942 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 2067943-2067995 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 2068003-2068156 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 2068230-2068378 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 2068379-2068563 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 2068564-2068673 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 2068677-2068704 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 2068708-2069375 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 2069376-2069698 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 2069700-2069946 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 2069947-2070027 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 2070141-2070392 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 2070901-2071179 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 2071180-2071354 2010 July-Aug (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 2071355-2072270 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 2071574 (1 of 3) 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 2071574 (2 of 3) 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 2071574 (3 of 3) 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 2071575-2072270 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 2072271-2072449 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 2072450-2072498 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 2072499-20733107 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 2073280-2073377 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 2073378-2078762 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 2078781-2078849 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 2078850-2078922 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 2078923-2079002 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 2079022-2079661 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 2079663-2080743 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 2080755-2081043 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 2081061-2081181 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 2081201-2081812 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - 2082202-2082871 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - 2082875-2083488 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 2083495-2083597 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - 2083608-2083680 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 2083685-2083805 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 2083807-2083859 2010 Aug (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 2083868-2083996 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 2084008-2084030 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 2084031-2084392 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 2084420-2084443 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 2084446-2084887 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 2084888-2085508 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 2085512-2085854 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 2085856-2086139 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 2086198-2086669 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 2086703-2086989 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 2086997-2087098 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 2087106-2087993 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 2088002-2089792 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 2089802-2090015 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 2090023-2091453 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 2091474-2092263 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 2092265-2092647 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 2092652-2092674 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 2092675-2093030 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 2093032-2093170 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 2093182-2093237 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 2093238-2093388 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 2093389-2093581 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 2093582-2093685 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 2093702-2093909 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 2093928-2093989 2010 Sept-Oct (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 2093911-2094376 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 2094412-2094645 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 2094646-2094656 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 2094657-2094803 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 2094863-2095091 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 2095093-2095217 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 2095218-2095254 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 2095261-2095468 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 2095469-2095508 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 2095509-2095735 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 2095736-2095977 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 2096019-2096040 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 2096042-2096048 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 2096049-2096062 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 2096063-2096175 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 2096176-2096212 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 2096222-2096306 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 2096308-2096397 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 2096519-2096552 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 2096553-2096620 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 2096621-2096752 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 2096754-2096881 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 2096882-2096893 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 2096897-2097352 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - 2097356-2097486 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - 2097555-2097599 2010 Oct (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 2097600-2097868 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 2097821-2098382 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 2098392-2098454 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 2098463-2098690 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 2098691-2098791 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2098792-2098917 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 2098919-2099016 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 2099017-2099171 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 2099173-2099523 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 2099524-2099544 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 2099550-2099665 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 2099666-2099753 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 2099803-2099909 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 2099910-2099956 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 2099960-2099991 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 2100015-2100066 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 2100155-2100310 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - 2100311-2100577 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 2100578-2100601 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - 2100602-2100828 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - 2100829-2100905 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 2100907-2100996 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - 2100998-2101259 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - 2101263-2101268 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - 2101269-2101335 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 2101336-2101446 2010 Nov-Dec (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - 2101528-2102081 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 2102084-2102102 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 2102103-2102240 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 2102241-2102299 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 2102302-2102571 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 2102572-2102652 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 2102653-2102755 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 2102756-2102814 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 2102816-2103060 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 2103061-2103226 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 2103227-2103289 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 2103261-2103354 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2103355-2103446 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 2103578-2103610 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 2103011-2103783 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 2103784-2103829 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 2103832-2104067 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 2104068-2104098 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 2104099 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 2104100-2104196 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 2104218-2104429 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 2104431-2104443 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 2104444-2104869 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 2104907-2104941 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 2104946-2105096 2010 Dec-2011 Jan (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 2105100-2105117 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 2105118-2105254 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 2105255-2105494 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 2105544-2105622 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 2105623-2105660 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 2105661-2105767 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 2105768-2105816 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 2105817-2105823 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 2105827-2106055 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 2106056-2106199 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 2106200-2106393 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 2106394-2106529 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 2106531-2106569 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 2106570-2106602 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 2106603 (1 of 2) 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 2106603 (2 of 2) 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 2106604-2106906 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 2107091-2107448 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 2107450-2107554 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 2107595-2107640 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 2107643-2107682 2011 Jan-Feb (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 2107743-2108164 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 2108165-2108364 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - 2108368-2108554 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 2108555-2108587 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 2108589-2108863 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 2108864-2109049 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 2109050-2109429 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 2109433-2109737 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 2109742-2109075 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 211079-2111095 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 2110146-2110296 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 2110300-2110876 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 2110878-2110933 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 2110936-211110 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 2111111-2111179 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - 2111182-2111196 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - 2111199-2111415 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 2111424-2111799 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - 2111801-2112108 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - 2112110-2112535 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 2112536-2113144 2011 Feb-Mar (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - 2113145-2113304 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 2113308-2113355 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 2113356-2113381 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 2113407-2113447 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 2113725-2114097 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 2114100-2114309 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 2114310-2114899 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 2114900-2115109 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 2115349-2116345 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 2116353-2116598 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 2116601-2116972 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 2116984-2117609 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2117611-2117782 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 2117792-2118335 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 2118339-2118519 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2118520-2118684 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2118730-2118899 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 2118902-2119450 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 2119457-2119958 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 2119520-2119958 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 2119960-2120471 2011 Mar (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 2120472-2120796 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 2120800-2121898 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2121905-2121968 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 2121969-2122981 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 2123011-2123776 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 2123778-2125021 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 2125026-2125166 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2125168-2125199 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 2125200-2125248 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 2125249-2125424 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 2120472-2120796 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 2120800-2121898 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2121905-2121968 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 2121969-2122981 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 2123011-2123776 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 2123778-2125021 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 2125026-2125166 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2125168-2125199 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 2125200-2125248 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 2125249-2125424 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 2125426 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 2125427-2125493 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 2125519-2125713 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 2125715-2125780 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 2125789-2125935 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 2125983-2126114 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 2126115-2126299 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - 2126300-2126362 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - 2126363-2126549 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 2126550-2126666 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 2126667-2127031 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - 2127032-2127316 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - 2127318-2127397 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - 2127400-2127427 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - 2126550-2126666 2011 Mar-May (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - 2127510-2127631 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 2127632-2127877 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2127878-2128232 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2128234-2128252 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 2128253-2128433 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2128253-2128433 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2128751-2129248 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 2129250-2129344 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 2129345-2129628 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 2129629-2129681 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 2129690-2129705 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 2129706-2129814 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 2129818-2130086 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 2130093-2130164 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 2130165-2130277 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 2130278-2130494 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 2130495-2130712 2011 May (Box 15, Folder 18)